Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/teja-reddy-330011169 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Freelance marketplace freelance C#

Teja Reddy

Chatbot Developer | Conversational AI | MS Azure | Bot Framework | Cognigy AI | Teneo AI | ChatGpt Integration

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Summary

Passionate software engineer with 5 years of experience in software design and development chatbots.

Excellent capability to explore, learn and understand newer technology.

Actively involved in all the phases of SDLC like design, development, testing, deployment and support.

Able to work in a team as we as independently producing desired results.

Experience

Tech Mahindra
Senior Software Engineer
November 2021 - Present (3 years 1 month)
Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Acuvate

Software Engineer
July 2018 - December 2021 (3 years 6 months)
Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Education

Joginpally B.R Engineering College sc, Computer Science · (November 2013 - 2017)